Guide to the Yale College Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of William Clyde Devane as dean, 1913-1965; Accession 1964-A-003
  - Associate Dean's Files
    - Problems of Yale student seminar: notes, 1950-1951 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Reading for summer, 1939-1961 (Box 18, Folder 33 - 34)
    - Religion and post-war Yale: committee on, 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Riot: ice cream, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Riot: snowball, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Rockerfeller Brothers Theological Fellowship Program, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - St. Marks School, 1950-1951 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Schoenberg Memorial prize, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Science III, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Selective Service, 1948-1957 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Senior Advisory Board: minutes, 1958 April-May (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Senior Society elections: correspondence and clippings, 1953-1954 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Undergraduate Activities Committee
      - Report re: budget for the committee, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 45)
      - On post-war undergraduate activities to the council of masters, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 46)
      - Report re: rules and suggestions governing fraternity activities, 1945-1947 (Box 19, Folder 47)
      - Report of the Torch Honor Society on various phases of student life at Yale, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 48)
      - Memorandum re: procesures, elections, organization and constitution, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Activities: minutes, 1945-1958 (Box 19, Folder 50 - 53)
    - General warnings: statistics, 1947-1956 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Assistant Dean Chauncey's Files
    - Alpha Delta House, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Day Panel, 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Magazine, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - American Political: magazine, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Annual report to the president, 1955-1963 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Architectural Magazine, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Reger Ascham Society, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Athletics -- Inter-collegiate: annual reports, 1959-1963 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Audio-Visual Center: Yale Cinema Association, 1954-1956 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Student bartending agency: Harvard student agencies, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Beaux Arts Ball, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Bladder ball, 1960-1962 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Bottoms Up (musical revue), 1963 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Censorships, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Charter bus, 1961-1963 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Charter flights, 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Chicago Business School Scholarship, 19657-1963 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Chi Psi, 1956-1963 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Civil Rights Coordinating Committee for Yale, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Class dinners, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Coaches Club, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Coats and Tie, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - College Weekend, 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Yale Coop Association Board, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 25A)
    - Courses, 1960-1963 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Crossroads Africa, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Campus Crusade for Christ, 1957-1962 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Dramatic Association, 1956-1965 (Box 20, Folder 29-30)
    - Dukane Orchestra, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Exchange of information: Yale policies and procedures, 1959-1963 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Facts: magazine, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Fraternity Advisory Committee, 1957-1963 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Fraternity Averages, 1958-1963 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Fraternities and discrimination, 1959-1960 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Fraternities and Rushing, 1958-1964 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Gate '67, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Goldwater for President committee, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Harvard Business School, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Heeling: participation in extracurricular activities, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Human Relations Council, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Society for Inter-American Affairs, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Junior Prom, 1953-1962 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Kansas City Club, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - The Moderator: magazine, 1960-1964 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Liberal Religious Fellowship, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - "Mixers", 1964 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Motor vehicles, 1951-1964 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Motor scooters, 1958-1964 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Musician's union, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - National Association of Student Personnel Administrators (NASPA), 1964 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - National Investigating Committee on Aerial Phenomena, 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - National Student Association, 1958-1963 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Northern Student Association, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Opera Association, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Orwell, George -- Forum, 1954-1965 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Outline Agency, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Peace Corps, 1962-1964 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Photography Club, 1959-1961 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Yale Political magazine, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 10-11)
    - Poll of student opinion, 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Posters, 1956-1963 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Psychology Department: experiments, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Rallies, 1957-1961 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Reading Society, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Research Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Reserve Officers Training Corp (ROTC)
      - 1959-1963 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Revolutionary personalities, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Rifle team, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Riots, 1959-1963 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Rostrum: published by Political Union at Yale, 1959-1965 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Russian seminar, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Ski team, 1959-1960 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, 1959-1964 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Sports Car Club, 1961-1963 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Squash Review, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Student organizations (defunct), 1957-1964 (Box 23, Folder 6-7)
    - Studies regarding Yale student graduates, 1959-1963 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Television station, 1954-1955 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Tours -- European, 1954-1964 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Town and Gown relations, 1959-1961 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - United Nations Model Assembly, 1957-1960 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Yale Station Review: magazine, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Wilkinson, John A., correspondence, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Young Americans For Freedom, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Records of Georges May as dean, circa 1936-1971; Accession 1980-A-017
  Restricted until January 1, 2047
  - A - General
    - 1956-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 2 - 3)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Academic freedom, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Admissions, Board of
    - 1951-1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Admissions, Office of
    - 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Admissions Policy Advisory Board, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Adult Education, Fund for, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Advanced Placement Conferences, 1967-1971 (Box 2, Folder 19 - 21)
  - Advisory Committee, Humanities, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Afro-American Studies
    - 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 25 - 26)
  - Albany - State University of New York, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Alumni Board
    - 1958-1965 Jun (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - 1965 Jul - 1966 Jun (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 31 - 32)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - American Council on Education, 1958-1961 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 1958-1961, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 37 - 38)
  - American Studies, 1947-1951 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Annual Reports
    - 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Anthropology
    - 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Archeology, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Architecture, 1959-1965 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Army and Air Force, 1953-1957, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Art and Architecture, 1968-1971 (Box 4, Folder 47 - 49)
  - Arts, creative, role of in undergraduate education, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Association of American Universities, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Association of Colleges in New England, 1951, 1956-1969 (Box 4, Folder 52 - 53)
  - Astronomy 10, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Athletics
    - 1965 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - 1966 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Athletics, Committee on Academic Obligations of, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Athletics Control Board
    - 1939-1962 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - 1968 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Athletics, Department of, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Athletics, Eligibility, 1944-1947 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Athletic Eligibility, Interuniversity Committee on, 1936-1951 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Automobile correspondence, 1956 June - 1958 October (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - B - General
    - 1950-1965, n. d. (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - B.A., experimental five year, 1965-1971 (Box 7, Folder 79 - 80)
  - B.A., Joint M.A.-B.A. Committee, 1963-1967 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - B.A., M.A./B.S.-M.S. Program, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 82 - 83)
  - Bergen (Francis) lectures, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Berkeley College, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 85 - 87)
  - Branford College, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 88 - 90)
  - Brewster, Kingman
    - 1963 Dec - 1965 Jun, no date (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Speeches, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Bryn-Mawr College - Institut D'Etudes Francaises D'Avignon, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Budgets, 1955-1971 (Box 8, Folder 100 - 102)
  - Buffalo, University of, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Bursar's Office, 1968-1971 (Box 8, Folder 104 - 106)
  - Business Manager
    - 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - re Campus Police, 1959 September 1 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - C - General
    - 1951-1965 (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Calendar, 1952-1968, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 118 - 120)
  - California, University of, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - Calhoun College
    - 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 123)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - Career Advisory Office, 1967-1971 (Box 9, Folder 126 - 128)
  - Carnegie Studies for Engineering, 1957-1960 (Box 9, Folder 130)
  - Carnegie Teaching Fellowships
    - 1957-1965 (Box 9, Folder 131)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 132)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 133 - 134)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 135)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 136)
  - Carroll, Richard C., 1965-1968 (Box 10, Folder 137 - 138)
  - Cars - Freshman, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 139)
  - Chauncey, Henry, Jr., 1964-1971 (Box 10, Folder 140 - 142)
  - Chinese Language School: military intelligence, 1942-1945 (Box 10, Folder 143)
  - Cinema, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - Civil Defense Program, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 145)
  - Classics, Department of
    - 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 146)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 147)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1970 (Box 10, Folder 149)
  - Coalition for a New University, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 150)
  - Co-Education at Yale
    - 1965 (Box 10, Folder 151)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 152)
    - 1969 (Box 10, Folder 153 - 154)
    - 1970 (Box 10, Folder 155 - 156)
  - College Deans, 1966-1971 (Box 11, Folder 158 - 160)
  - College discussion courses, 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 161)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 162)
  - College Seminar Committee
    - 1969 (Box 11, Folder 163)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 164 - 165)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 166 - 167)
  - College seminars for juniors and seniors, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 168)
  - Combined major: literature, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 169)
  - Combined major: science, 1968-1969, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 170 - 171)
  - Committees, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 172)
  - Committees, 1968-1972 (Box 12, Folder 173)
  - Comptroller's Office, 1966-1971 (Box 12, Folder 174 - 175)
  - Computer Science, Department of, 1967-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 176 - 177)
  - Concilium on International Studies
    - 1960-1963 (Box 12, Folder 178)
    - 1963-1965 (Box 12, Folder 179)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 180)
    - 1967 (Box 13, Folder 182, Box 12, Folder 181)
    - 1968 (Box 13, Folder 183 - 184)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 185 - 186)
    - 1971 (Box 13, Folder 187)
  - Concilium on International Studies: faculty research
    - 1965 (Box 13, Folder 188)
    - 1966 (Box 13, Folder 189)
    - 1967 (Box 14, Folder 190)
    - 1968 (Box 14, Folder 191)
    - 1969 (Box 14, Folder 192 - 193)
    - 1970 (Box 14, Folder 194)
  - Corporation votes, 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 195 - 196)
  - Council of Masters
    - 1958-1963 (Box 14, Folder 197)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - 1965-1966 May (Box 15, Folder 199)
    - 1966 Sep - Dec (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - 1967 (Box 15, Folder 201 - 202)
    - 1968 (Box 15, Folder 203 - 205)
    - 1969 (Box 16, Folder 206 - 207)
    - 1970 (Box 16, Folder 208 - 209)
    - 1971 (Box 16, Folder 210)
  - Counseling, Placement and Research, Office of, 1958-1964 (Box 16, Folder 211)
  - Course of Study Committee
    - 1952-1959 (Box 16, Folder 212)
    - 1960-1965 (Box 16, Folder 213)
    - 1966 (Box 16, Folder 214)
    - 1967 (Box 16, Folder 215)
    - 1968 (Box 17, Folder 216 - 217)
    - 1969 (Box 17, Folder 218 - 222)
    - 1970 (Box 17, Folder 223)
    - 1970 (Box 18, Folder 224)
    - 1971 (Box 18, Folder 225)
  - Course of Study Committee, Executive Committee: student members, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 226)
  - D - General
    - 1957-1965 (Box 18, Folder 228)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 229)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 18, Folder 230)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 231)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 232)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 233)
  - Daily News, 1966-1970 (Box 18, Folder 234 - 236)
  - Davenport College (Box 19, Folder 242)
  - Dean's Office, Yale College
    - 1936-1948 (Box 19, Folder 243)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 244)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 245)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 246)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 247)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 248)
    - alterations, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 249)
    - annual report, 1949-1966 (Box 19, Folder 250)
    - search committee, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 252)
  - Deans of Residential Colleges
    - 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 253)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 254)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 255)
    - prospective, 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 256 - 257)
  - Debating and Public Speaking, 1952-1966 (Box 20, Folder 258 - 259)
  - Development Office, 1958-1970 (Box 20, Folder 260 - 262)
  - Directed Studies
    - 1949-1959 (Box 20, Folder 263)
    - 1960 (Box 20, Folder 264)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 265)
    - 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 266)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 267)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 20, Folder 268)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 269)
    - 1970 (Box 20, Folder 270)
  - Directed Studies in Science, 1957-1960 (Box 20, Folder 271)
  - Directors of Undergraduate Studies, 1968-1971 (Box 21, Folder 272 - 274)
  - Divisional Major
    - 1950-1965 (Box 21, Folder 276)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 277)
  - History, the arts and letters, 1966-1969 (Box 21, Folder 278 - 279)
  - Political Science and Economics, 1966-1969 (Box 21, Folder 280 - 281)
  - Culture and Behavior, 1966-1970 (Box 21, Folder 282 - 284)
  - Divisional Major IV, 1966, undated (Box 21, Folder 285)
  - Dramatic Association, 1950-1966 (Box 21, Folder 286 - 287)
  - Dramatic Association: Report on examination of accounts, 1958, 1959, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 288)
  - Timothy Dwight College, 1967-1971 (Box 22, Folder 289 - 290)
  - E - General
    - 1958-1965 (Box 22, Folder 291)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 292)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 22, Folder 293)
    - 1969 (Box 22, Folder 294)
    - 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 295)
  - Early Concentration Program, 1964-1966, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 296 - 298)
  - Economics Department, 1958-1966, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 299 - 301)
  - Education, 1963-1965 (Box 22, Folder 302)
  - Educational Research, Office of
    - 1961-1962 May (Box 22, Folder 303)
    - 1962 Jun - 1965 (Box 22, Folder 304)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 305)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 22, Folder 306)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 307)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 308)
  - Jonathan Edwards College, 1967-1971 (Box 23, Folder 309 - 310)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, Department of
    - 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 311)
    - 1968 (Box 23, Folder 312)
    - 1969 (Box 23, Folder 313)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 314)
  - Engineering, School of, 1955-1965 (Box 23, Folder 315)
  - English as a foreign language, 1965-1970 (Box 23, Folder 316 - 317)
  - English, Department of, 1957-1965, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 318 - 319)
  - Enrollment figures, 1951-1957 (Box 23, Folder 320)
  - Environmental Studies, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 321)
  - Executive Committee, Elementary and Secondary Education, 1965-1968 (Box 23, Folder 322 - 323)
    Records of the executive committee are restricted until January 1, 2044
  - Executive Committee, Faculty of Arts and Sciences
    Records of the executive committee are restricted 75 years from the date of their creation.
    - 1944-1957 (Box 24, Folder 324 - 325)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 326 - 327)
    - 1958-1961 (Box 24, Folder 328 - 329)
    - minutes and correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 24, Folder 330)
    - correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 331)
    - minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 25, Folder 332)
    - correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 333 - 334)
    - minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 335)
    - correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 25, Folder 336)
    - minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 25, Folder 337)
    - correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 338)
    - minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 339)
    - correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 340)
    - minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 341)
    - agendas, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 342)
    - correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 343)
    - correspondence (Monday meetings), 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 344)
    - correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 26, Folder 345 - 346)
    - minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 347)
    - minutes and related correspondence, 1974 September-December (Box 27, Folder 348)
    - minutes, 1975 January-May (Box 27, Folder 349)
    - Survey of Disciplinary Actions Undertaken by the Executive Committee of Yale College and the Rules Committee of the Freshman Year 1958-1963 (Box 27, Folder 350)
    - "Report on Consultations at Several Universities Relating to the Administration and the Faculty" (confidential), 1958 (Box 27, Folder 351)
  - Executive Committee, Yale College
    Records of the executive committee are restricted for 75 years from the date of their creation.
    - 1959-1961 May (Box 27, Folder 352)
    - 1961 Jun-1963 (Box 27, Folder 353)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 354)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 27, Folder 355)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 356)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 357)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 358)
  - F - General
    - 1957-1965 (Box 27, Folder 359)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 360)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 28, Folder 361)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder 362)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 363)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 28, Folder 364)
  - Faculty, evaluation of, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder 365 - 366)
  - Faculty handbook, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 367)
  - Faculty, Yale College: minutes, 1948-1951, 1955-1966 (Box 28, Folder 368 - 370)
  - Fellowships, Committee on, Yale College
    - 1957-1965 (Box 28, Folder 371)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 28, Folder 372)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 28, Folder 373)
    - 1969 (Box 28, Folder 374)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 375)
  - Financial Aid Office, 1962-1963, 1967-1969 (Box 29, Folder 376 - 377)
  - Foreign Fellowships Committee, 1965-1968 (Box 29, Folder 379 - 380)
  - Foreign Area Studies, 1944-1945 (Box 29, Folder 381)
  - Form letters, 1948-1960, 1963-1966, undated (Box 29, Folder 382 - 384)
  - Fraternities, 1955-1965 (Box 29, Folder 385 - 386)
  - Free School, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 387)
  - Freshman counselors
    - 1965 (Box 29, Folder 388)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder 389)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 390)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 391)
  - Freshman: faculty program advisor
    - 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 392)
    - 1957-1963 (Box 30, Folder 393)
    - 1963-1965 (Box 30, Folder 394)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 395)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 30, Folder 396)
  - Freshman Year, Committee on, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 397)
  - Fulbright Fellowships, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 398)
  - G - General
    - 1956-1965 (Box 31, Folder 410)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 31, Folder 411)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 31, Folder 412)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 413)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 414)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 415)
  - Geography, Department of, 1956-1958 (Box 31, Folder 416)
  - Gimbel High Scholarship cup, 1956-1971 (Box 31, Folder 418)
  - Goethe Project, 1947-1958 (Box 32, Folder 419)
  - Governance, Study Commission on, 1969-1971 (Box 32, Folder 420 - 421)
  - Grade analysis, 1948-1949 (Box 32, Folder 422)
  - Grading system, pass-fail, 1967-1970 (Box 32, Folder 423 - 424)
  - Graduate School
    - 1961-1964 (Box 32, Folder 425)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 32, Folder 426)
    - 1966-1 968 (Box 32, Folder 427)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 32, Folder 428)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 429)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 430)
  - Graduation
    - 1949-1965 (Box 32, Folder 431)
    - 1966-1969 (Box 32, Folder 432)
    - 1970 (Box 32, Folder 433)
    - 1971 (Box 32, Folder 434)
  - Griswold, President A. Whitney, 1951-1962 (Box 32, Folder 435)
  - H - General
    - 1956-1965 (Box 33, Folder 441)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 33, Folder 442)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 443)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 33, Folder 444)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 445)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 446)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 447)
  - Harvard University
    - 1950-1961 (Box 33, Folder 448)
    - 1963-1966 (Box 33, Folder 449)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 450)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 451)
  - Health, Department of University
    - 1954-1965 (Box 33, Folder 452)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 453)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 34, Folder 454)
    - 1969 (Box 34, Folder 455)
  - Health Service, Yale University, 1967-1968 (Box 34, Folder 456)